<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://lightwithin.richardkemp.uk/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://lightwithin.richardkemp.uk/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-03-21T20:15:59+00:00</updated><id>https://lightwithin.richardkemp.uk/feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Light From Within</title><subtitle>{&quot;en&quot;=&gt;&quot;Diet coaching authentic to you and your truth&quot;, &quot;el&quot;=&gt;&quot;Διατροφική καθοδήγηση αυθεντική σε εσένα και την αλήθεια σου&quot;}</subtitle><author><name>Your Name</name></author><entry><title type="html">Welcome to The Light From Within!</title><link href="https://lightwithin.richardkemp.uk/update/2025/01/28/welcome-to-TLW.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to The Light From Within!" /><published>2025-01-28T20:58:43+00:00</published><updated>2025-01-28T20:58:43+00:00</updated><id>https://lightwithin.richardkemp.uk/update/2025/01/28/welcome-to-TLW</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://lightwithin.richardkemp.uk/update/2025/01/28/welcome-to-TLW.html"><![CDATA[<p>I’m so excited to share this moment with you. After years of guiding individuals toward food freedom and body trust, I’m thrilled to officially launch <strong>The Light From Within</strong> website—a space dedicated to helping you reconnect with your body’s wisdom and rediscover the joy of eating.</p>

<p>This isn’t just a website; it’s a sanctuary. A place where you can let go of diet culture’s noise and begin to hear your own voice again. Whether you’re healing from years of dieting, struggling with emotional eating, or simply craving a more peaceful relationship with food, this is your invitation to start anew.</p>

<p>One of the things I’m most passionate about is making this work accessible and meaningful for everyone. That’s why I’m proud to offer my coaching services in <strong>both English and Greek</strong>. No matter where you are in the world or what language feels most like home, I’m here to support you.</p>

<p>If you’re ready to explore what it means to live freely, to eat intuitively, and to trust yourself fully, I’d love to walk this path with you. Let’s start this journey together.</p>

<p>With love and gratitude,<br />
<strong>Eleni Vantana</strong><br />
<em>Founder of The Light From Within</em></p>

<hr />

<p><em>Your light is already within you. Let’s uncover it together.</em></p>]]></content><author><name>Your Name</name></author><category term="update" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m so excited to share this moment with you. After years of guiding individuals toward food freedom and body trust, I’m thrilled to officially launch The Light From Within website—a space dedicated to helping you reconnect with your body’s wisdom and rediscover the joy of eating.]]></summary></entry></feed>